utrechtart.com 2014-07-02

# Privacy Policy - Art Supplies from Utrecht featuring fine art supplies, school art supplies, discount art supplies, artist paints brushes, acrylics, watercolor supplies, artist oil paints, artist canvas and more

| | 

## Website Information

For every visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the email address (where possible). 

We collect only the domain name, but not the email address of visitors to our website, the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, user-specific information about the pages accessed or visited, and information volunteered by the consumer, such as preferences, survey information, and/or site registrations. 

The information we collect may be used to customize the content and/or layout of our website for each individual visitor and to notify visitors about updates to our website.

In addition, information (including name, address, and transaction information) may be shared with agents or contractors who assist in providing support for our internal operations, and used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes. 

##  Cookies 

With respect to cookies, we use them to store visitor preferences, to record session information (such as items that consumers add to their shopping carts), to record user-specific information about the pages users access or visit, to alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, and to record past activity in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site. 

##  Email 

If you wish to be removed from our email marketing list, please log in to your account and click on the "Email Preferences" tab. Select the "Change Preferences" option to access and edit your email subscription status. If you do not have a registered account on our website, you may contact us by email at [info@utrecht.com, ](mailto:info@utrecht.com)by phone at 1-800-223-9132, or by mail at: [](mailto:info@utrecht.com)Utrecht Art Supplies  
PO Box 1267   
Galesburg, IL 61402-1267[](mailto:info@utrecht.com)

##  Mailing 

If you supply us with your postal address, you may receive periodic mailings from us containing information about new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive these mailings, please let us know by sending us an email or calling us at 1-800-223-9132. [](mailto:info@utrecht.com)

##  Phone Calls 

Customers who supply us with their telephone numbers may be contacted by phone regarding order status, product availability, payment information, delivery information, new products and services, or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such calls, please email us at [info@utrecht.com](mailto:info@utrecht.com) or call us at 1-800-223-9132. [](mailto:info@utrecht.com)We do not share the phone numbers of our customers with other organizations. [  
](mailto:info@utrecht.com)

##  Use of Information 

Information that you give us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. This information may also be shared with other marketers to bring you offers of interest. 

If you do not wish to have your information shared, please let us know by emailing us at [info@utrecht.com](mailto:info@utrecht.com) or calling us at 1-800-223-9132. 

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some future time, we will post the policy changes on our website and provide you with the opportunity to opt out of these uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please visit our website for periodic updates. 

##  Disclosure 

The information we collect may be disclosed when we are legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website. 

## California Shine the Light Law

Under California's "Shine the Light" law (Civil Code Section 1798.83), California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain, once per calendar year, information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year. To obtain this information from us, please use the Customer Service link below and then the Contact Us link, write "Request for California Privacy Information" on the subject line of your message, and we will send you a reply email containing the requested information. Not all information-sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

## Children

We do not knowingly collect personally-identifiable information from children under the age of 13. The site is not directed at children under the age of 13, and by using the site, you represent that you are not under the age of 13.

## Right to Transfer

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary set forth in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to disclose and/or transfer your personal information to a third party in connection with a proposed or actual purchase, sale, merger, or any other type of acquisition or financing of all or any portion of Utrecht.

## Pixel Tags

We use pixel tags (also known as a clear GIF or web beacon) to analyze online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our website. Through a pixel tag we can determine information about your visit to our website, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you access, and other information. This information may include your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to our site.

##  Company Information: 

Utrecht Art Supplies   
PO Box 1267    
Galesburg, IL 61402-1267   
1-800-223-9132   
Customer Service   
 www.utrechtart.com   
| |
